Yes, it has started.
Good evening, everyone. The morning challenge has begun. We are,
I'm Ebisu Shiritsu.
Before we begin, we would like to choose today's MC.
Please vote for 1 or 2, whichever you prefer.
The person holding the number card with the number written on it is the MC.
Okay, then, let's start voting.
Let's start.
I would like to present today's program in a very slow and relaxed manner.
Yes, I see.
Yuno smashed the lens of Nonoka's glasses.
That's right. I don't know how to do it, but I did it.
I didn't know how to do it, so I asked her to do it for me.
I did it easily.
It was easy!
Are you voting?
I think we're voting.
We're both voting.
I don't know.
I have an image that Yuno is the MC for the showroom.
I have the image of Yuno being the MC in a showroom.
But when it comes to polls like this...
I don't know how they know.
That's why I'm going to show it to you like this.
You always hide it with your hand.
I see.
So maybe they can see you.
Then it's time to vote.
Five.
Four. - Four.
Three.
Two.
One... yes... yes... yes... yes... yes...
Yes, which one?
Which is it?
It's me.
Let's see...
You're early. It's early.
Oh, it's going up fast.
That's why
I have a Japanese exercise bill.
Yes, sir.
Inoue is today's MC
I look forward to working with you.
Pleased to meet you.
It was Inoue this time, too, wasn't it?
Everyone knew... it was Yuna... right?
I'm going to stop even giving them to you from now on.
Yes, let's do that
I'll be your MC today, Yuna Kunimoya.
Good luck!
Let's start the showroom, the 68th EBITCHU's Delightful Showroom.
Today is the 68th Ebichu's
Ebichu no Ebichu no Ebichu no Ebichu no
Thank you very much for visiting Ebitu's Delightful and Fufufu Showroom!
Ebichu's Delightful and Fufufu Showroom is
Our little sister
It is the sisterhood of Uka's showroom.
So, it is time to spread the word here.
I'm going to make an announcement on the official X of Ebichu now so that as many people as possible can see this distribution,
Please spread the word.
Okay, Yuka-san's.
It's okay to wear glasses, right?
Glasses.
Yes, cheese.
Thank you very much. Well, you're wearing glasses with NONO. Yes, sir. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
And you're still doing a bad crab.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm going to do this project today.
It's called
Hilarious and ho-hum survey talk.
Yay! Yay!
Before you do a talk, you take a survey to decide what you're going to talk about.
That's the questionnaire talk.
Yes, sir.
I've done this many times in my shows.
This time, the theme is like this.
We've thought about it, and we've come up with this.
We want to talk about this, we want to talk about that, we definitely want to talk about that, but feel free to vote for your favorite, ladies and gentlemen.
We'll let you decide...
I can see the bottom of the page, you can see the letters. I wonder which one of you wrote it.
I don't know. I don't know.
He wants to hear 8 episodes.
We'll be happy if you choose 8 episodes.
We'll be happy.
I don't know.
Ready, five, four, three, two, one.
Here we go.
Sumida not Santa!
Let's see what happens now.
Thank you, episode 8.
This is a talk topic that I'd like to discuss with you.
On May 9th
Handshake Member Auction Photo Book will be released!
It's a first.
Just a handshake.
Since September? I've done it with the five younger members, and I've also done it solo,
I've also been featured in UptoBoys a few times,
I've also had a couple of times on UpToBoys, but I've compiled them into this album, so there are some images that you haven't seen yet, and some costumes that have never been shown to the public,
Please look forward to it. Also, on May 6, we will be holding a release commemorative event at the 5th floor of the Tower Records Shibuya store.
The event will be held on the 5th floor of Tower Records Shibuya. We are looking forward to seeing you there.
We are still waiting for you. I'm still waiting for you all. There's still a place to go home and stuff.
Here is the announcement. This is Tana's announcement. Um, I'd like to make an announcement, and, um, yes, and also...
Is it on the board? Upto-boy, Yuno's grandma opened it like this on the morning of the release and her mom sent it to me to take a picture of her.
You're so cute, grandma. You stood up for me. You're so cute, grandma. You're so cute, Grandma. You got up, didn't you? You're a grandma, aren't you? That's right.
We went to the spa and everything.
Yes! That's right.
It was really like we were all going on a school trip together, and we had a lot of fun filming it.
Which part was fun? Where was the fun?
Yeah, but..,
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, my God, it's just here.
Yeah, but I, uh..,
Oh, I don't know about this. I'll take that one. I'll take that one. I'm only here, so I'll just put this out.
I'll take that one.
I'm doing a pillow fight on the futon.
Maybe they're doing a pyramid.
I think there's a picture of him on X or something.
I think it was on X or something.
The cameraman said, "We're going to shoot after this.
The photographer warned us that there would be more shots after this.
We had a lot of fun... we had a candy party and everything.
It was fun. It's been a while since I've been back, hasn't it?
February? Yeah, so we all gathered at 5:00 in the morning in Ebisu or Shibuya, and we all got on the bus with the cameraman and all the staff.
We all got together with the photographers and all the staff, and got on the bus.
Yes! It was fun.
It was so much fun.
It's a collection of photos that really show the real you.
The makeup and everything is pretty natural.
Hair is also straightened.
I think you'll be able to see us as we really are.
Okay, let's go then, shall we?
I was so happy because I didn't get to experience a real school trip.
I don't mean that I haven't experienced it very often, but it happens only once every three years.
Not that everyone has so many of them.
Yes.
Yes, I did.
The photo book had a surprisingly large number of pages, didn't it?
Yes, it was something like that.
It's very large.
Yes, we had a chance to look at it before it was completed.
There were a lot of good, good, good things in the book.
And there are also interviews, so there are personal stories.
They are talking about it, talking about it, talking about it, etc.
So, by all means, please come! By all means, by all means.
Please, please, please.
Next, five, four, three, two, one, done!
Okay, which one is it?
Number one!
15th Anniversary Tour, Ichikawa & Omiya!
This is the spring tour that has started, finally started.
I don't know, what do you think?
I'm going to spoil it, aren't I?
Yes, it is. We've only started the tour in Detachment.
So, there are a lot of people who haven't come yet, and those who have come, they're either at home, or they're happy with the house, or they're not.
I'm sure there will be a lot of Soul D'Art, and the next one will be in Sendai on the 29th, and there are only a few tickets left.
I'll go to Sendai too if I can.
Thank you so much!
I'm going to the encore in Ichikawa... and I'm announcing the Saitama Super Arena...
But you know, I don't know if I told you...
I don't know if I mentioned it, but we knew about it.
We'll do the same thing at the rehearsal.
We practice.
We're going to go through the bike, and we're going to go through the venue outside, and we're going to go through the venue inside.
We don't want the audience outside to hear us or the people who are keeping the bikes.
So, Rika-chan would say, "Yes, I'm going to make an SSA presentation," and then the SSA announcement would be signaled with a bang, and then a phosphorus type of signal would be issued,
She wanted to rehearse it, so she said, "What's your favorite Misto, Honey Churro," and then she let out a bang, right?
It was fun. I was the last student to go there on the day of the taste sensation, that blue lemon.
Riko said, "I'm going to Saitama, I'm going to Saitama!
I'm doing it... but if you think about it... it has to be Saitama Super Arena.
I understand SSA and so on, but Saitama, you know.
It is Saitama, isn't it?
We were able to go to Saitama on the next day.
Yes, we were able to go there with all 10 of us.
But I don't know about this time.
But this time, we are touring with the album,
I don't know what to say.
Of course we will play songs from the album,
I won't say "Dre," but we're playing them.
Yes, we do.
And the songs that are on the call video,
I don't say "dre", but I do it. I'm not saying it's a dre, but I'm doing it.
I'm doing it.
But you know what?
I heard a lot of calls for the first song,
I was happy.
I also thought that the performance this time had an interesting structure and a sense of speed.
There were cool songs, too, and the usual fun, flirty songs during the eves,
The director for this production is Mr. Yusuke, who does things like college alerts, and he is really doing a great job.
He's doing it, he's doing it, he's doing it, he's doing it.
He really thought of a lot of song connections and stuff like that.
Thanks to him, many of the songs from the album fit in well with the previous songs.
Yes! That's amazing! I feel like thank you very much.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's amazing to see such a wide range of songs in one live performance.
That song was a moving performance, and I'm sure the audience got it.
I think the people who came to the show understood that song.
If you haven't come yet, please look forward to what's to come!
I'll announce it later, so please look forward to it!
Remember the calls.
If you remember the calls, we'll lead the way.
If you do the call, you'll feel like you're having fun with us, so we'd love it if you do it.
So we would be happy if everyone could do it, so if you come with us, or even if it's you, you can learn it. Even if it's not perfect, you can just say, "I feel like I was here.
It's okay if you just have a vague idea, because it's easier to understand the first song or something.
So all the members would be happy if you could take a look at it, even if it's just a little bit.
Yes, we will be very happy. Thank you very much.
I'll announce it later.
Next.
Start.
If you bring a sense of fun,
I think it's probably a good idea,
And you naturally want to interact with them,
Yeah, for sure.
Cute costumes, beautiful.
Yes, for sure.
You're already doing it.
I think you've posted it on your Instagram or something, but you're wearing a white outfit.
Yes, it's Menkara. Yes, I'm Menkara, but it's a white costume, and if the spotlight or something is on Menkara, it's white again. Yes, menkara. Yes, I am a menkara, but if I have a white costume and the spotlight is on the menkara, it becomes white again.
So it's really interesting because it's like I'm wearing white wings.
If I made a mistake in this, but I think that's fine.
It was fine as long as you were confident.
I didn't show the call video, but they called for the song. I was so happy to know that this is how the calls were made.
I was so happy, and I was wowed as I was doing it. I hope you can see the call videos as just an indicator.
Okay, five, four, three, two, one, zero.
Okay, next.
Seven.
What's 7?
Tell me.
I don't know LU.
This is the theme of my talk.
As I've mentioned on my blog...
I'm not very good at baking.
I gave you some kind of auto-mail, didn't I?
But I even burnt them.
I'm a little burnt.
It's not as perfect as I wanted it to be.
I have the image that you make a lot of Valentine's Day decorations.
That's true.
Also, we often talk about it among the members.
"I made this at night.
Yes.
I'd love to hear your cooking tips.
Tips?
I only cook for the members.
That's what's so great about it.
I don't know how you do it.
I make it while imagining what it would taste like if I put it in.
Ah...
Yesterday, I ate fried green pepper, ham, mentsuyu, and a little sesame oil.
It was absolutely delicious!
Wow!
That's amazing! It's really great!
I don't know...
I have an image of you making sweets, too. I have an image of him making sweets.
But he can also cook a proper dish, or rather, a side dish.
Tasting is important! I sometimes go for raw rice for sweets, though.
By the way, do you sell sweets in the same quantity as Meg's? I'm sure I can get away with a little more than that for sweets.
From experience.
But I'll make sure to measure it properly.
Also, there are some that are really short on butter.
I'm not going to say, "If you have it, that's enough.
I want to do my best.
I want to work hard.
You gave up on preheating, didn't you?
I had to do it in the oven. It was a pain in the ass.
I thought I could do it in the toaster, and I did, but I burned it.
That's the point, I guess.
Let's just go for it for once and try to follow the instructions.
That's right.
Ingredients and stuff, you know, I'm putting it in exactly as it's supposed to be,
That's not good, because it's a pain in the ass in a weird way.
That's it, probably.
That's right.
Is there anything that's easy to make?
That's strange. But I don't care what it is.
It's crazy. But I think cookies are pretty easy, but... you know... that was back when Aya and Cocona were all together, right?
Aya and Cocona were talking about Valentine's Day, right?
When they were talking...
They're happy, that's what I'm thinking.
That's right, and then they can't make cookies.
The cookies turn into bread.
What do you mean? He's like, "What do you mean?
I'm going to make cookies.
If they turn out to be bread, I don't want to be with those two, so I'll do my best not to turn out to be bread.
If it turns out to be bread, you can hide it.
That's right. I'll hide it from them and say, "It turned out perfectly.
I don't understand what you mean by "it will turn into bread.
What do you mean?
I don't know what I did to make it become bread.
I'm not good at it, so I'll do my best to be good at it, so please teach me.
Yes, I'll teach you anytime. I'll teach you anytime.
It's amazing you can make bread.
I don't think so.
I think he said something about no baking powder.
He said he used the right amount.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. Okay, let's start the next one.
He said you can pick the ones you've done, but some of them are hard to talk about.
Some of them might not be very C-wordy.
He said the recipes aren't good. - That's true.
That's true.
I've been watching TikTok lately, and they're popping up, aren't they?
It's amazing, isn't it?
But I feel like people who don't like to cook tend to choose the hardest ones.
I think people who aren't good at cooking tend to choose difficult recipes because they don't have experience.
They think they can do it, so they choose the hard ones.
I made ambergris the other day. Wow!
It turned out perfectly.
It's just agar and sugar.
Amazing!
It's delicious.
I'll let you know what the vile time is this year.
Countdown!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Which one?
Number 3.
Laforet Harajuku Collaboration
This is...
It's a collaboration.
I'll tell you about it later.
From May 1st to 7th
On the 5th floor of Laforet Harajuku On the 5th floor of Laforet Harajuku
I'm having them collaborate with me.
Last time I went to the store, right?
There is a collaboration menu cookies, drinks and ice cream?
It was delicious!
Was the drink good? Was it good?
The cookies are for the younger members and the drinks are for the older members and the younger members.
But I liked Mayama-san's drink as it was at home.
Really? What flavor was it?
What was it? Was it something like lavender?
Lavender...I kinda forgot
It was delicious.
Yeah, but we can all get a drink and a cookie.
You're talking about how smart we are.
I'm sure you'll want to buy some.
But the cookies were all different flavors.
What flavor? What flavor?
I like chocolate chip.
Chocolate chip.
The standard kind? Chocolate chip, like chocolate chip.
Sometimes it's the standard kind.
Yes.
And sometimes it's matcha.
Matcha and coconut.
You can have a drink and a cookie or an ice cream
and eating cookies and ice cream...
Yeah.
There's also one-piece dresses and stuff.
Yes! I tried on a dress, and so did we.
It was cute.
Yeah, and we were cute, too. We were cute.
Also, my chocolate chip cookies had a texture like the chunk cookies that are popular now, so if you are interested in trying them, please go try them.
They are tiny versions of the ones you see on TikTok and other places where people from overseas dip a big one like this in milk and eat it.
Yes! A tiny version of the ones they dip in milk, and yes, ice cream too!
The ice cream is quite hearty.
That alone is enough to fill you up!
If you like chocolate mint, you'll love it!
You should try it! You should eat it.
Cymange or something that looked good.
Or ring lights.
Yeah.
Like a ring.
What's that?
It's amazing, isn't it?
They seem to sell all kinds of goods.
Yeah.
They're selling all kinds of stuff, so...
Please look forward to it.
What kind of merchandise do you mean?
I mean, are there any pictures, or acstas?
We'll have acuta, so please wait for it.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
I'm sure there are people who have never tried ChocoMeat.
Please try it during the Ebi Chuo period!
Don't hate it!
But it's not that strong.
You may be able to eat it even if you don't like it.
It's summer and it's warm, so maybe I'm not supposed to talk about it?
Really?
I'm sorry.
Neruyosan came to see me.
Well, well, well... now that I'm here, I'll tell you all about it.
Okay, I'll tell you.
It's summer and it's cool and delicious.
There is coolness, so look forward to it.
Well, I guess it's okay now that you're gone. Okay, I'll go to the next one.
Here you go, start survey.
It's okay to munch on the mints.
Go ahead and eat.
So far, they've been kind enough to go without being covered.
What do you think?
what do you think?
Okay, so 5
Four. 4
OK.
Yes, followed by
Number five.
On the Disney C.
I'm talking about me again.
A long time ago, in January.
I went to Disney C with Emana.
it was pretty crowded.
So
I tried to get on Indiana John's first.
I tried to get on Indiana John's.
But there was a line at the bridge.
I tried to get on Indiana John's, but there was a line at the bridge, so I wondered if it was Indiana John's. I was in the very end of the line, so I asked if it was Indiana John's,
So I asked the guy at the very end of the line if this was IndyJohns,
He said, "Oh, this is Little Green Man.
It was a little embarrassing, wasn't it?
It was a little food.
I said, "Oh, I'm sorry," and went to get in line at Indy Joe's.
We were going to finish the ride.
Then I wanted to ride Raging Spirits.
And there, too, it's kind of close, you know, location-wise.
And there was another bridge.
I thought, "This time, this bridge must be the Raging Spirits line.
I asked the guy at the psycho-commissary, and he said, "This is Turkey Lick." Turkey Lick is also a little game.
And Turkey Rick, too, because he's popular with the little game.
I told him that I was so embarrassed... and then I asked him about it, and he said, "This is Turkey Rick...
It was very embarrassing.
That's it.
What was that?
Yes, that's right.
I went to the used bathroom here.
But were you okay with the screaming?
Well, we were having a showdown at Raging Spirits to see who could scream the prettiest. Yeah, well, we had a showdown in Raging Spirits to see how beautiful we could make our voices sound.
I don't know.
We practiced lip rolls and stuff like that.
We practiced lip rolls and stuff like that, and then we had to scream in a beautiful voice, but it was cold that day, so we had to go down in the rain.
But it was cold that day, and it started to rain during the show.
That's right.
And after the scream, it came in a big puff of smoke,
It's cold! I had to ride it while screaming "It's cold!
I couldn't keep up with the three of them,
I just couldn't keep up with the three of them.
The three of them have their own worldview, and it's very interesting.
It was an embarrassing story at Disney.
That was my embarrassing story at Disney.
Shall we move on to the next story?
Yes, please.
Let's start.
It's hard to ride with three people.
That's true.
When five of us go on a ride, it's 221.
We would go on a roller coaster or something like that.
We didn't have much of a choice.
Like 10%.
We decided on 9% and 10%.
Baymax ride,
Yuna was the only one who could ride it,
Yuna rode alone,
And she could see the people around her,
And everyone was dancing.
And the people on the ride were dancing, too.
It was really amazing.
But Yuna was dancing by herself, too.
How about this?
Five, four, three, two, one, zero.
Yes, followed by...
Number 4!
This is Maratan Yuno.
This is Yuno, Mire-chan and Yuna at Marathon in Omiya! This is a picture of Yuno, Mire-chan and Yuna at Mar-a-La-Tan in Omiya.
Yuna, Mire-chan and Yuna?
Yes, I went to Ma-la-tang with Mire-chan and Yuna.
Is there a lot of food there, and you have to pick it up yourself?
Yes, that's right.
There are a lot of restaurants like that in Mara Thang.
3 yen per gram?
Yes, yes, yes.
Just like that.
There are a lot of ingredients.
Yu's...
I put a quail egg, tomato and bean sprouts.
You can choose how spicy you want it.
Yui wasn't in the mood for spicy food, so she chose zero spiciness.
Yes, yes, yes.
Zero spiciness and chicken soup?
Wow!
It's not spicy at all, but it tastes good, and I've been addicted to the taste since I had it,
I wanted to eat it alone at home the other day, so I made it the day before yesterday.
Where did you get it from?
From what?
Chicken paitan soup.
Oh!
But you have to cook the chicken properly.
Chicken broth, milk, sesame oil...
It's so good.
Wow! That's amazing.
It tastes just like the ones I had at Mile Art's.
Oceanic.
But that's because it's a restaurant, so it tastes like what you'd get at a proper restaurant, but it's a restaurant.
But that's because it's a restaurant, and they cook it properly. But I can't wait to go back.
A new type of chicken pie is unusual.
I've met a restaurant that I've been to before, too, for their tomato soup.
Is that so? Oh yeah, the chicken. Yes, it's kind of like that when it's zero spicy. But it's not a very simple taste, but it's still a tare-glass soup,
And I didn't spend that much time making it,
I want to make it someday.
Chicken stew.
Yes, it's good. Yeah, that's fine.
Please come then.
We will go with the eating line. I'll be waiting.
Yes, I see. It's delicious with thick vermicelli. Please come then, I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting for you.
It's delicious with thick vermicelli.
At that time, the price changes depending on the gram, right?
Do I have to spend a higher price?
I haven't had it recently.
I'm glad you're okay with it.
When I went to Maratha with Yuna-san, we had a case of over 2,000 yen because we ate too much toppings.
I had an incident when I went to Maratha with Yuna and ate too much topi and the price exceeded 2,000 yen, so I want to be careful.
I don't think Yuna has that problem.
Yuna stayed within 1,000 yen.
That's too amazing. I'm the one who should be careful, right?
I only had about 1,000 yen with me.
I see.
Then I guess the next two.
Yes, let's go. I'll make the next one last.
Okay, let's go to the next one.
I'll tell you everything I've told you about 6 and maybe tomorrow.
I'm going to be there at 56:00, but I'm going to be in there at 56:00. IH, leave it. 54320, then.
Let's see who's nice to me.
Oh, everyone is nice! This is Yuno's story.
Yuno went to take pictures of Nonoka the other day.
You went to take pictures?
Yes, to take pictures.
You went to take pictures.
Yes, you took pictures.
Yes, we took pictures.
And the cherry blossoms were in full bloom.
Yes.
And it was raining the day before.
Right.
It looked like the cherry blossoms might have fallen,
I put it in the story,
I didn't put it in the story anymore, but the one I'm going to put in the photo book that Yuno is going to make, isn't that amazing?
Isn't that amazing? That was amazing!
You can already see the clarity and the breathtaking beauty.
And there was also a center photo, which is usually the case, but this one was straight white one-piece with a green bag.
Yuno prepared the costumes, and she had two camera lenses, a film camera, and an electronic camera. What about Yuno, when she just joined? When Emi-chan first joined, everyone wore a backpack.
It had been years since I saw that backpack, and it made me really nostalgic. I told her I really liked it.
He had been wearing a tiny backpack since before Emmaena joined the group.
Yes, yes, yes, yes. I was allowed to wear a backpack.
So, Sakura, you know, so there were food stalls and stuff...
This time we went to Tamagawa.
I went to Tamagawa this time, and I saw a food stall in the beautiful weather.
What was it called? What was it called? Baby caspera?
It was delicious.
It was delicious! It was so good!
They had oden.
Why don't you show me?
Someday, I'll finish it.
I'm not sure why they didn't show it to us. to say, "Why don't you put this out already?
I don't want to show it this time.
Maybe I'll put it on a good person.
I might post the photos I saw that Yuno liked.
So please look forward to it.
The beauty of the momentum
I may not post it until I can release it someday, so please post the beauty of the momentum until I can release it someday.
Please look forward to it. I'm still thinking about the title, so I'm not going to announce it yet.
But right now, Yuna was taking pictures the other day, right?
I think Yuna is still planning to take many more pictures, so please look forward to them.
I'm going to tell you all about it.
The theme is to write a cherry blossom tree with one stroke for those who couldn't see the cherry blossoms! Theme 3: Pretend to be a principal and give a speech to new students in New York City!
to discuss the theme and the number one spring song by Ebichu Theme After Theme Ask listeners what they plan to do during Golden Week. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Well, which one, but he said we can decide this one. Which one do you want to do? So...
We were talking earlier, right? I was talking about it earlier. We talked about the April Fool's Day project. Right. I couldn't lie properly. I couldn't lie properly.
April Fool's Day project. Let's lie about everything and answer the questions.
I'll reply to all the comments with my true feelings.
It was the day of the announcement of the "difficult path" that I couldn't choose.
I have to send difficult questions.
What's your eyesight?
Five. - Three.
What's your favorite candy?My favorite snack is
Karamucho.
Oh, wait, that's a tough one.
How many millimeters is your head?
0.5 mm.
What should I bring to the sky?
A heart that won't call.
What would you like to eat now?
Well, red hot sauce.
You don't want to eat?
I just want something spicy right now.
It's difficult.
You didn't like it best in the photo book?
Yes, seriously. You didn't like it? Yes, I did.
I wouldn't normally say I didn't like it.
I see. I see.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Are those glasses real?
They're real.
Yes, they are.
Which country would you like to visit?
Where would you like to go?
It's not good.
What about patents?
Arithmetic.
What do you do when you wake up in the morning?
Running.
How much of a hand measure is that? Twenty.
Twenty? What time is it? It's 6:00 in the morning.
It's important.
Should I not go to Sendai? I don't think you should go.
I don't think you should go, there's only a few days left.
I don't think you should go.
I'm lying.
I'm telling the truth.
If you had the whole day off, what would you do?
Sleep. I'm going to bed.
I'm thinking of buying a black Vazcan.
Should I?
In the first place, the figures are correct, aren't they?
It's right... it's right...
I didn't go to the Village Vanguard in Shibuya yesterday.
I didn't see Yuno's autograph and autographed book section right next to the cash register.
I see.
There were not many Yuno's autographs and autograph books.
Please don't go there!
Your birthday is March 20th.
No, it's not!
Should I go to HMM in Shibuya?
Nonaka and Riko's autographs are there, but I don't have any autographs, so I don't think I should go. Nobuka and Riko have autographs, but I don't have their autographs.
I don't have her autograph, but I don't think you should go.
I don't think you should go.
Is it Yuna's birthday?
Not at all.
Not even close.
This is a tough one.
It's not a good idea to go to a state you don't want to go to, regardless of the nationality of the state.
The 100-year member photo book is...
This one's not too cute.
And it's not packed with too many things.
I wouldn't buy it.
So, what would you like, Rust?
Rust.
What's the SSA's part?
You're pointing it at me.
I was going to skip that one.
SSA, yes.
The best.
The best stew... A good place to love stew...
That's all I have to say. I heard in the comments that you and the principal were talking about ramen.
Last time, after the rehearsal in Ichikawa, Yuno, Cocona, Mirue and Fujii took me to a ramen restaurant.
That's right.
If you want to go, you can go. It was like, if you want to go, go ahead.
It was delicious.
It was so good.
I like it. Eat a lot of food.
There he goes.
What do you want to do?
Go on, then.
So there's a number one, huh, guys?
I'm sure we all have our own arguments.
We're going to discuss the number one spring song in all of Ebichu, and we're going to ask you to tell us your favorite ecchi-maru song.
So we're going to talk about the number one spring song in all of Ebichu, and we're going to ask you to tell us what your favorite sex song is, and what's your favorite hurricane song, and what's your favorite song?
Oh!
What else?
Crystal Drop, which I remember every time it snows.
Has it already passed? Winter?
Yeah, uh...
I wonder which one it is.
What? Do you mean in the middle of the snow?
The middle of it.
I seem to remember.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So does Wolatia.
Yes, Wolatia too.
Plum, indeed.
Plum?
Oh, I see.
Plum trees, yes... oh, yes, winter plum trees are your favorite.
You all like...
And winter love, too.
I see.
Tissues are also spring.
That's right.
Well...
Let's see what you like.
Joint?
All season long. If there is an all-season...
Yeah, right.
Sure, let's hold hands.
Summer Glitter is just like the title says.
Yes, it is summer.
But still...
I guess this is a spring play in my mind, too.
Ah...
I'm not sure...
I don't know when it was... in March... there was a day when it was raining really hard.
There was a day when it rained really hard.
I was listening to a spring storm on my way home.
I was soaking wet and it felt so good.
I went home listening to it and felt good.
So it was a spring storm.
Do you have a favorite? Spring storm... it was a spring storm, wasn't it? Yeah. It was a spring storm. Do you have a favorite? Springtime.
Uh, yeah, but maybe it's a spring storm right now.
Yeah.
That one was really good, with the choreography and everything.
And we like Drower?
Two years ago?
We did a lot of work on "Drower," but not since then?
We had an MC at the end of Drower, and the next one was, you know, that one. That was the big Donnen team.
Oh, I see. That's right.
That's right. So when the drama ended with everyone holding hands at the end,
And they were all running beside each other.
That's right.
I was Hinata-chan next to him, so I ran along with them.
Yes, that's right.
Chikumo-san, now that there are nine of us, or something like that, now that there are nine of us...
First Rika-chan would walk over and cross.
We ran backwards or forwards.
That part was difficult.
We had a lot of trouble with that part.
I'm looking forward to seeing how it will turn out when we have 10 members.
I'm looking forward to it.
The nine of us were running around like crazy.
It was close, wasn't it? That was close, wasn't it?
I was going coon and going through.
I don't know.
I don't know if we'll see it this year.
I've never done the cherry blossom goround, even with nine people.
I've never done it.
I sang at my nativity, but
I haven't sung it.
We haven't even choreographed it with 10 members yet, so I don't know if we have it yet, or if we even have it in the first place.
It would be nice if we could someday.
But at the end of the spring tour, this is a spoiler, but the encore changes every day, doesn't it? Yes, that's right. We play a different song each time.
Maybe it will come someday.
That's for sure.
I don't know exactly when.
But it might come someday.
I think it would be good if they come to all the shows.
If you come to all the shows, yes, I know
I couldn't make it to the next show at all.
Maybe it would be good if we did
Please come
To lose your frustration, you have to come to all of them
The spring of Mass training was great too.
You did it.
I was streaming that on LINE LIVE.
I miss it.
Last year already.
That's right.
It's been a year.
That's scary!
That was fast.
So fast!
You know what?
It's not a lot, it's just five of us.
That song is one of the toughest songs to sing and dance to. So it was really hard for the five of us to sing the chorus.
It was tough. Everyone sang the choruses.
I wonder what was the most popular song for everyone. Harumura? I don't know what we sang a lot. But everyone was equally plum, I used to see plum and spring storm? I saw a lot of plum blossoms. I think there were a lot of comments earlier.
I don't know how much of the spring songs are included in the shoe laces and fan files, depending on who you ask. I think there were more drawers full of shoelaces and fanfiles, too.
Yes, in the drawer. Yes, in the drawer.
I was in the drawer the whole time.
Spring Storm was in the middle of the show. Did it change in the middle?
Spring Storm was changed in the middle.
But I think the shoelaces and the fan file were always in there.
Everybody's doing it.
Is there a Spring Storm? Did it become a love rental?
Oh, no. No?
What is it?
Love Rentals has changed?
Love rentals. What did I say about renting love now? What is it? Ai no Rental has changed?
Ai no Rental.
What do they call it now?
Yeah, they're dancing.
It's like they're dancing a lot.
To put it plainly...
I'm wearing the white woman's outfit behind the perfume.
I'd like to draw your attention to that as well.
And we're going to do our best to make that our testimony, and we're going to dance and express ourselves on the day.
After the show, we'll have a medley of spring songs for everyone to enjoy, and I hope you'll feel a lot of spring in your hearts.
Yes!
This is the end of the 68th edition of the delightful and unfunny showroom in the sea. Here are the announcements. There are quite a lot of announcements. It was hard work to write them, wasn't it? I did my best. OTHER SIDE OF INDEKA HOUR has started, and the next one will be in Sendai on April 29.
It will be in Sendai on April 29. So little time left. So, first of all, I'd like to say "Thank you very much.
So, first of all. Fukuoka and Niigata for Yuna's triumphant return. That's right.
The rice is delicious. Delicious.
Pop-yaki is also delicious. There are lots of delicious foods.
I would be very happy if you could really come on a trip.
Yes, I would.
Yes, so we are looking forward to seeing you. We have tickets again, so please come.
Let's get bigger and bigger for SSA.
We will do our best.
Yes, this is ?
This is the Private Ebisu University x Ebisu Family Taiwan Main Trip 2024.
Yes, this is ? This week is the school trip 2024!
We will be going to various places for dinner, and we will be able to go together like a real fan tour,
It's going to be like an eminent school trip, so please come and join us,
We will also have a live concert in Taipei on July 6, so I wonder if there are people who are watching from Taiwan right now?
That's great! Thank you very much. I am sure you will make memories for the rest of your life, so please come!That's great! Thank you so much. This is really, really, really going to be the memory of my life, so I really hope
I hope you all come. We can also make a pilgrimage to the holy land of the National Defense Book, and we can make pineapple cakes together.
The FC selection reception will be open until 23:59 on May 1, and the general reception will start on May 20, so please come and have an experience that will never happen again.
I'll do my best now and then.
And here it is... the official photo book of the members of the Shei-Chey Bisscher School will be released on May 9, 2024.
And the event to celebrate its release will be held at the 5th event space of Tower Records Shibuya Store.
There are still some places where you can buy tickets.
There are still some places where you can buy tickets, but the date, time, and time is still up in the air.
Please come to the event and tell us what you think of the photo book and the spring tour.
or your impressions of the spring tour
or "I'm going to Taiwan", etc.
I would be very happy if you could report on your daily life.
I'll be waiting for it. I'm waiting for it. I'll be waiting. And last but not least.
The Ebichu pop-up store will be held from May 1 to May 7 at Laforet Harajuku's 5th make-the-stage. Is it during the Golden Week holidays?
Yes.
If you are not doing it during Golden Week, please come and see us.
We have a collaboration menu and goods, and they are all very cute,
Please come and feel the EBITCHU. Please make plans for EBITCHU.
Please make a schedule for Ebichu.
Yes, please make a schedule for Ebichu.
Yes. So, that's it. Now I would like to see the final ranking top 5
Yes, 5th place, thank you, Shinkai-san!
Thank you very much, Zukki-san in 4th place Thank you very much, Gomikakko Momijiya's ramen is the best in the world in 3rd place
Thank you, Setoka-san in 2nd place. Thank you very much.
1, Mr. Bug. Thank you very much.
Yes, so ends the 68th edition of Ebituna's Delightful and Fufu Showroom.
The end.
Yes, it's over.
Please wait for the next installment, which will be announced as soon as it is decided.
That's all for now, this is Private Ebichuak.
Bye bye.